um you know, two of kind of what I would
call our our short list players um to
pick up uh another top 100 pick as well
as another pick in the top 150. Um you
know, we were very pleased with with um
just really all the activity this
evening. We're really excited about
Spencer. Um you know, and his potential
at left tackle. He's super athletic,
very versatile, uh elite makeup. And
then KC, he's um you know, he's dynamic.
He's uh you know an outstanding
separator, really good with the ball in
his hands. Uh honestly probably the best
punt returner in this class. You know
those two guys will will really help our
offense moving forward. So with that
open up for questions.
it was and uh you know we were joking
it's like okay well the board probably
fell better than it did in our
simulations in the in the week leading
up to it which is always nice. Um, but
we we're really excited about the two
players uh that we got and we're really
excited that um you know we were able to
pick up the extra draft re while
coveted at nine.
>> Andrew, how many did you get a lot of
calls for six or and Casey was the best
one or or you know, how'd that kind of
go when you were on the clock?
>> We did get several calls for six. Um,
you know, we thought through, um, I
should say this, we got several calls,
uh, for six and nine, the combination of
six and nine. Um, at six, um, you know,
Kansas City made the made the most sense
because it was a big enough move where
we could pick up resources, um, but also
small enough with what had happened on
the board that, you know, we could we
could get, um, you know, one of our
short list of of targets, of which, you
know, Spencer was at the top. Um, and
then at nine, we did get a little bit of
action there as well. Um, but nothing
that necessarily compelled us to move
off at the pick.
>> I know you kind of believe a tackle is
tackle, but in Spencer's case, does it
help that you've seen him play on the
left side?
>> Yeah, you know, it c it certainly helps.
Um, but really you're looking more for
traits in that regard, Dan, just
because, you know, if you think about
side to the right side all the time and
it never gets talked about. Um, and that
distinction, it's just, you know, you
need two of them to pass protect. And
one you maybe help a little, the other
you help a little bit more. Um, but
Spencer, he's he's super athletic. He's
he's played on both sides. He's really
smart. We're excited to have him.
>> Hey, Andrew. And Andrew, uh, Casey had
some drops and are you concerned about
about that? Yeah, every receiver besides
maybe Larry Fitzgerald has a couple
drops and um you know Casey, he's been a
dynamic producer at NC State, Texas&M
um you know he he's he's electric with
the ball in his hands and uh we're
looking forward to having him
this season
the versatility that he has. Um, was
that really intentional for you this off
season with maybe what has happened with
the offensive line the last couple of
years? It just feels like versatility
was like a top your wish list for every
player that you brought in in that
position.
>> I'd say if you're on the O line, you you
typically need to be able to play two
spots. I'd say probably more so than
versatility. It was resiliency within
the O line in terms of how you build
that position group. Um, versatility is
one way to do it. Strength and numbers
is is another way to do it. Um, you
know, I think we'll be in a position
where we have both. You know, with
Spencer in particular, look, we're
looking to park him at left tackle and
let him play. So, um, while it's nice
that he's played several spots, that's
not our vision for him.
>> Um, I know he played inside and out. Do
you envision him being able to play both
roles for you?
>> Yeah, we do.
>> Read the letters that he wrote. um just
how impressive is it that able to get
where he has given all he's grown up
with including the start?
>> Yeah, that's one that's one thing that
we talked about. I I told him um you
know when he was on his his 30 visit, I
think it's incredible what he's what
he's overcome and gone through in his
life. Um when when we got the uh you
know, his agent sent the letter, I'm
sure, you know, every GM, but um I
actually went I I called him after the
letter. I was like, "Hey, look, I I
thought that was really awesome." And
that that was separate from, you know,
obviously liking him as a prospect. But
um you I told I'll share one story. When
Casey visited, I was like, "Hey, I hope
you're a Brown, but if you're not, I
sure hope you're in the NFC because I
don't want to face you." And then I told
his agent afterwards was I look, hey,
everything that that kid's about,
everything that he's overcome, um you
know, if he's not here, he just needs to
know he's got a fan. Just I I really
love the person. Um and he's obviously a
dynamic football player. Was his punt
return ability just a bonus or did it
put him over the top among other
receivers left?
>> I'd say it was a I'd say it was a bonus,
you know, more than anything, Tony,
because um it's certainly great if you
can, you know, if you can get the ball
and play Marcus in a variety of ways. It
allows you to be more explosive as a
team, allows you to score more points.
Uh but also being realistic that you
know if you look at former let's say
high pick receivers whether it's you
Deshawn Jackson back in the day Dez
Bryan early in his career you know
usually at some point they probably like
play their way off of that. So like it's
not necessarily bankable for their
entire career. Um but with Casey it
certainly was an added bonus.
you had Spencer
number one amongst your targets, but did
you give much thought to Jordan Tyson
and was, you know, a little difficult at
that moment to trade away from him at
all or did you know that you were
targeting Spencer?
>> You know, we we liked a number of those
guys up there, including Jordan. Um, you
know, but but Spencer was our really
really our top, excuse me, Spencer was
our top target at that point. Um, a lot
was made about Spencer's arm length. Um,
I was curious when you watched the film
how much that was like a a talking point
and maybe what are the the traits that
you think will allow that to not be be
an issue in the NFL?
>> Yeah, I know it gets talked about a lot
and I remember, you know, the, you know,
the legendary, you know, O line coach,
uh, Dante Scarnia with New England used
to say it's just it's way overrated.
Think most times tackles get beat for a
lack of feet or athleticism or anchor or
awareness, you know, as opposed to
length. Um, the biggest thing is like,
hey, how can the guys, you know, short
the corner and with elite athletes like
Spencer, they do it with their movement
skills. Maybe if you have a guy that
just is not as quick or not as agile,
then length is a little bit more
important. Um, but the difference in his
success isn't going to be, you know,
this in terms of in terms of arm length.
He has a number of incredible
um both physical and mental
characteristics that we think will lead
to a successful transition.
>> But how do you measure when you have
like a dynam dynamic athlete like KC but
guys drop guys drop balls? How do you
kind of measure that?
>> Yeah, it it's it's it's really relative
to the population. Like I know that gets
you know that gets talked about but he
has natural dexterity. Um, you know,
it's nothing it's nothing extreme or
nothing out of u uh
I guess it's not an it's not an outlier,
you know, relative to to other receivers
in the draft class. I know that's been
the primary talking point, but we're
we're comfortable with Casey's hands.
>> He drove to Cleveland. Was he in fact
your first 30 visit?
>> Uh, great question, Tony.
I don't know if he was our first. He was
among our first. Um, but we had we had a
couple of guys in right after the right
after the combine. He was one of them. I
I don't I don't think he was the very
first, but he was among our first. Yes.
>> Did you
>> Let me go Mary Kay and then I'll go
Zach.
>> Do you envision using all the remaining
drafties that you have now that you
picked up the
>> Look, I I would hope to draft in volume
this year, but it really just depends on
how the board falls. So, I'm I'm also
like depending on how good of a review
you guys write us. I'm going to use that
seventh rounder. If you guys write
something. Okay. [laughter]
>> Did Todd and you to an extent see some Z
Flowers and how Todd used him?
>> You know, I do think there are I do
think there are some similarities in
terms of like the movement skills, the
twitch. Honestly, some of the questions
regarding the hands coming out, you
know, Terry. Um, you know, I think the
one thing that maybe gets a little bit
lost is like Ki is a much bigger uh, you
know, player than Z, but I think there
is some overlap in the characteristics.
Um, you know, I think you look if we get
a player who's comparable to Z Flowers,
you know, when we're sitting here from
three years, we'll be elated.
>> Let's go back to Spencer. I mean, early
on, I guess how early on in this process
had you guys really zeroed in on him as
the top tackle in a pretty deep class.
You know, we we used the whole process,
Ashley. You know, we we did feel like
Spencer was, you know, unique in terms
of, you know, everything that comprised
his um onfield performance, his physical
skills, and and his makeup. Um but, you
know, we we do like to use the whole
shot clock.
>> The terms of the trade with KC, was that
an option to get a 2027 pick?
>> No. No.
>> An extra third round pick
>> there. there was no option or discussion
of future picks.
>> I know it wind up only being two picks
that you didn't know. What's that
nervous level like saying, "Okay, you
want Spencer, but there's a chance." I
mean, were you worried at all that seven
and eight could take him?
>> You know, that's part of the risk. got,
you know, when we were on the clock at
six, you know, what I told the room is,
hey, there are there are really kind of
three guys left that, you know, we'd be
elated with, you know, if we had to sit
and pick. Um, moving back three spots
and having an idea of of where Kansas
City was going, we knew we were going to
get one of those three guys. Um, we also
felt the teams behind us, you know,
Washington, you know, they extended
Tonsel, they drafted Josh Connorly in
the first round last year. Um, New
Orleans, they drafted Kelvin Banks, you
know, at nine last year and then Fuaga
the year before that. So, we felt pretty
comfortable that a tackle wasn't going
to go unless a team traded into it. But
if one did, you know, we we we felt good
with the group of players that were in
front of us.
>> Able to contain his excitement upstairs
now his new best friend with get him.
Uh,
>> I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't see hear
who you mentioned.
>> Todd's reaction upstairs, you know, the
first round. Was he able to contain his
excitement?
>> He was he was pretty pumped up. He was
pretty pumped up. So, we we all were.
Um, you know, look, you don't always
have the board, you know, fall away that
you that you predict. And look, the idea
is like, you know, these guys, they
still have to they haven't hit the
grass. They still have to perform at our
level. But it's, you know, it's it's a
it's a start that we are excited about
because of the players and the people.
He me Spencer mentioned Joe Thomas and
just how much he looks up to him and
everything. How much are you guys going
to try to do you try to fac you know
facilitate getting those two together?
You know I know Joe's got his own
schedule and everything but how much do
you try to get those two together?
>> Yeah, you know Joe's Joe's obviously one
of our distinguished alumnists and he's
he's always um you know involved in in
in our O linemen. Um, also there's
there's a connection with with Joe and
um, you know, Spencer's, you know,
representation, but you know, we we love
I think you all know we love having Joe
around here and everything like that.
Uh, I'm sure he will have words of
wisdom for for Spencer and um, you know,
that's definitely a connection we will
look to make.
>> Let me go here first, Jeff, and then
I'll come back to you.
>> You obviously talked so much leading up
to the drafts just about not being, you
know, crippled by needs versus best
player available. Sort of that strategy.
um when when push came to show,
especially when you were on the clock at
six, like how were those what were those
conversations like and sort of deciding
what was there and what your needs were?
Because as it turned out, you obviously
did end up addressing some of your big
needs today.
>> There really wasn't a ton of
conversation. You know, all those
conversations happened beforehand. Like
at this point, it's like I would almost
make the quote of like calling plays.
You you talk through all those different
scenarios ahead of time. Um, and this
one was straightforward because, um, you
know, we viewed Spencer as one of the
top prospects in the draft. So, um, it
it made it pretty easy. There was, you
know, we didn't really feel like there
was any type of trade-off in that
regard. Go ahead, Jeeoff. Can
>> you just reflect, Andrew, on how you've
rebuilt the offensive line here in these
last two months? Yeah, I I think we are
very excited about the players that
we've brought in as well as the
development that's occurring with, you
know, existing players. Um, you know,
obviously the, you know, the vets that
that we acquired, whether it's via trade
or or free agency or, you know, with the
cap cut, um, we felt like we've we've
brought quality production, um, you
know, as well as as experience to that
group. Um, and then obviously with night
one adding Spencer, we think that's a,
you know, a big, um, you know,
foundational piece to that position
group. Um, we'll see where we go from
here. Look, we still have nine more
picks. Um, you know, we may not be done,
you know, with the O line at that point.
Um, and like I said, we're excited about
uh, some of our younger guys that are
going to get greater opportunities, but
um, it's a good start.
You talked about the traits with
Spencer, but I know to be a great O
line, there's some personality aspect,
right? Some nasty that the guy has to
have. Can you sort of speak to that side
of Spencer and what you guys learned
about him? Yeah, I think one of the cool
things about Spencer is you you can you
look at how um I guess scheme
transcendent he's been because what they
did his uh in 24 versus 25 was a lot
honestly was like a lot different in
terms of how they structured the run
game, how they did, you know, pass pro
and um you can see him move, you can see
him. Um, I think he's he's very gifted
and very versatile in that regard. And
um, you know, don't be fooled by his
kindness when you meet him. Have you
guys zoom with him already? Yeah. Don't
be fooled by his kindness. He's he's
he's he's nasty on the field. So,
>> all right.
>> You know what? I I watched the uh I
watched the Penguins game uh yesterday,
but I missed the brawl. I I turned it
before the for the brawl. They were up
one nothing, so I must have just missed
it when I flipped it. So,
>> yeah, it's pretty good.
>> See, Jeff's always my hockey guy. All
right. All right, guys. See you tomorrow
night.